Shark happens!
Sharknado 2: The Second One is a thriller, science fiction, tv
movie film directed by Anthony C. Ferrante.
A freak weather system turns its deadly fury on New York City, unleashing a Sharknado on the population
and its most cherished, iconic sites - and only Fin and April can save the Big Apple.
Fin Shepard, played by Ian Ziering.
Skye, played by Vivica A. Fox.
April Wexler, played by Tara Reid.
Ben, played by Judd Hirsch.
Mora Brody, played by Courtney Baxter.
Ellen Brody, played by Kari Wührer.
Sharknado 2: The Second One is a 2014 American made-for-television film and a sequel to the 2013
television film Sharknado and the second installment in the Sharknado film series.
It was directed by Anthony C.
Ferrante, with Ian Ziering and Tara Reid reprising
their roles from the first film.
The film premiered on July 30, 2014, and was the
highest-premiering film on the Syfy Channel.
In the film, Fin Shepard travels to New York with April Wexler and
attempts to stop a group of sharknadoes that appear there.
The third film, Sharknado 3: Oh Hell No!, was released on July 22, 2015.
The film explores themes of sequel, creature, shark,
creature feature, disaster movie.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.